In any area of your life that you find difficult to penetrate,
I want you to raise your prayer mantle, prayer sword and begin to part, divide
and make a way where there is no way.
Are you ready with me?
Every word you are going to speak at this moment – be anointed, in the name of Jesus!
Every word that will come out of your voice, your utterances – be anointed, in the name of Jesus!
When your word is anointed, you can divide
and make a way where there is no way in your business,
and make a way where there is no way in your career,
and make a way where there is no way in your finances,
and make a way where there is no way in your health,
and make a way where there is no way in your career,
and make a way where there is no way in your marriage.
Open your lips and begin to talk now.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Come out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I command every difficulty to be surmounted!
Your challenges – be surmounted!
Your situation – be surmounted!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I entered through the back.
She initiated her with my things, with blood.
The grandmother gave her to me at birth.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I made her do evil things.
Many powers.
Many demons.
I have many powers.
Power of manipulation.
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in Jesus’ name!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Mrs Ionara
Brazilian Living in Tenerife
She said her name is Ionara. She is from Brazil but right now living in Spain.
I am here to give glory to God because last week, I was set free.
I was delivered from the spirit of witchcraft because my grandmother worked with evil spirits.
I want to give thanks to God because one week ago, I was delivered from evil powers
that my grandmother used to work with as a witchdoctor - evil, satanic powers.
I was delivered from this spirit of witchcraft one week ago.
I was initiated from my mother’s womb by my grandmother who was a witchdoctor
and wanted me to inherit the evil powers.
As a witchdoctor, she worked with more than 20 demonic powers.
When I was in my mother’s womb, she would touch my mother’s stomach and chant.
When I was born, I was kept for seven days and set aside where nobody could touch me.
After seven days, a ritual was performed on me to dedicate me to satan and his demons.
After that, I was kept aside for 40 days and nobody was allowed to come near me.
She said that this started when she was in her mother's womb.
Her grandmother who was a withdoctor actually dedicated her to satan.
When she was in her mother's womb, her grandmother would be touching the stomach of her mother,
chanting to the evil powers.
Later when the child was born - when she was 7 days old,
the grandmother came and did a ritual.
After that, she was kept separate in a place so that people could not see the baby
until she was 40 days old.
This was a ritual to dedicate her to satan.
As a child, I would spend the weekends at my grandmother’s house and would follow her.
Because I was a child virgin, the black magic and charms would work quicker.
The animal sacrifices would work faster if I performed the rituals.
She said that when she was very small, she went to live with her grandmother who was a witchdoctor.
She began to be an assistant to the grandmother because she was very young and a virgin.
Because of that, it was easier for her to do those charms.
That was why the evil powers would work quicker through her.
So her grandmother used her as an assistant.
My grandmother worked with black, white and red magic, african magic and gypsy magic
and many more, including evil spirits such as leviathan.
Every weekend, she would be with the grandmother.
She would be doing this witchdoctor work.
So much so that even the names of the spirit -
her grandmother worked with so many evil spirits, different kinds of magic.
For example, black magic, red magic, african magic.
All of this was the type of witchcraft her grandmother was doing and she was doing it with her.
I started to grow in this environment where every day, I would witness this witchcraft.
She would perform rituals and offer sacrifices of animals to the evil spirits.
She would also present alcohol, tobacco and fruit to the spirits at an altar in one room.
My grandmother would also go to the cemetery to practise witchcraft.
I would assist her spiritually by doing the rituals and every day, I learned more from her
and I would begin to hear and feel the spirits.
If I needed something, I would go to the altar in my grandmother’s room and listen to them.
She said that as she was growing up with her grandmother,
there was a demonic altar in the house
and there was a separate room to worship these evil spirits.
She was the one who would do the offerings, rituals
because her grandmother would always send her to do it.
So she began working with these evil spirits.
She could even recognise their voice and feel their presence.
The grandmother used to go to the cemetery and call up the spirits of dead people.
She used to work together with her grandmother in all of this.
So she learnt how to do the witchcraft, the rituals.
Her grandmother was training her day by day for her to work with these evil powers.
As I grew up, I discovered that my grandmother possessed many powers and I also possessed them.
I was like I was playing with fire as I didn’t really know what I was doing.
For example, if I kissed a boy, he would be possessed with the spirit of lust and start fornicating.
I would seduce these men with my eyes.
She said that as she continued to practise this witchcraft,
she also began doing her own charms
and also using these witchcraft powers in her own life.
For example, she was getting more powers herself.
Just an example: If she wanted to be with a man, as young as she was,
she would command the power for the man to come.
After kissing that man, the spirit of lust would enter that man
and he would fornicate with many other women.
If any of my friends hurt me or made me feel bad or uncomfortable,
when my grandmother was doing witchcraft, I would invoke the spirits to harm them
and take revenge for me.
She said that if anyone hurt, abused or insulted her - even at school or her friends -
she would call their name whilst doing these satanic rituals in order to revenge on them.
So she would want harm to come to them.
As she called their name at these charms and rituals,
it would come to pass in their life.
When I was 14 or 15 years old, I began to like one boy and I did witchcraft on him.
When I started to go out with him, I told my grandmother and she called him,
sacrificed animals and did a blood covenant to join us together.
After that, I married him and gave birth to a baby boy.
She said at the age of 14 or 15, there was a boy that she liked.
So she told the grandmother and the grandmother did some witchcraft
so that she and this boy would be joined together spiritually in a satanic covenant -
also using blood, they were joined together.
My grandmother told me that each year, I had to repeat the ritual.
Because the marriage was not based on love but on charm, it would weaken each year.
I went to live in another city and I didn’t renew the charms so the marriage got weaker.
She said that her grandmother told her that in order for this marriage to stay,
each year, she had to renew the satanic covenant
because it was a satanic covenant joining the two of them together.
But she did not renew it.
So she realised it was not real love; they were only together because of witchcraft.
Soon, she began to grow apart from that man.
And she actually went to live in another city.
because the satanic bond started losing its power and the marriage started falling apart.
I moved to Spain to live with him and my son but soon afterwards, we divorced.
He went back to Brazil, my son went to live with my mum in Brazil and I stayed in Spain.
I travelled from Galicia to Tenerife where I met my current husband.
She said that soon she moved to Spain with her husband but after that, they divorced.
She left him and her child went to live with her mother in Brazil while she stayed in Spain.
Because I did not continue with the witchcraft, the evil spirits started attacking me.
I was tormented by depression and the spirit of suicide; I tried to take my life.
I thought my life was worth nothing and everything I did good was seen as bad.
These evil spirits started attacking me in a really strong way.
She said that whilst she was living in Spain, as she was not practising this witchraft anymore,
those evil spirits began to torment her in a terrible way.
She said that she would have a spirit of suicide
where thoughts would come to her mind, telling her to kill herself.
She would have depression that these spirits would not allow her to rest
because she had been serving them for many years and now she wanted to leave,
they continued to attack and torment her so her life was worth nothing.
I had a spirit of control and manipulation and would get angry if I didn’t have my own way.
In my anger, I would hurt my husband and others because I was influenced by evil spirits.
She said that she met another man and married again.
But still the tormenting of these evil spirits continued.
She had a power of control and manipulation.
She wanted to control her husband.
She did many bad things to him because of those evil spirits that continued to torment her.
Then, my husband took me to a church for the first time but I couldn’t stay there.
I developed headaches and started to cry and wanted to leave.
She said that she had never been in a church in her life before.
When she entered one church in Spain, she was not able to stay inside.
Her head hurt, she felt like vomiting, she wanted to leave
because all the evil spirits inside of her would not allow her to be inside the church.
That is why when she tried to keep coming back to a church, she kept running away.
Then I went to another church and the pastors told me about T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV.
They organised a trip to visit The SCOAN where we came last week and God delivered me.
She said that finally, she went to a church in Spain where they talked to her about T.B. Joshua
and they said they were planning a visit, to come to The SCOAN.
So she decided that she must come on that visit
and that is where she came last week and received her deliverance.
Mrs Ionara
Deliverance Testimony
Can you tell us exactly what happened during the mass prayer last week?
We saw on the screen how the Spirit of God took control in your life.
Can you tell us what was your experience?
Mrs Ionara
Deliverance Testimony
When Prophet T.B. Joshua was praying, I wanted to leave and run to the doors.
Before I knew it, I was at the front and was very angry and I felt like something left me.
Once it had left me with a scream, I found myself on the floor breathing heavily and calm.
She said that during the mass prayer, she felt so uncomfortable that she wanted to leave.
She even tried to leave.
Then she found out that the man of God was coming to the side where she was.
She wanted to go to the back but as she went to the back,
someone pushed her forward and that was where that evil spirit began to manifest.
She said she felt such anger inside of her.
Then, she found herself on the floor.
From there, I know that those spirits from my grandmother disappeared. I am delivered.
I feel different like a weight has come off my shoulders.
I feel light.
She said that since her deliverance last week, she feels totally free.
That it is like a huge weight has dropped from her body.
Now she feels free, happy and changed.
And she knows that something has come out of her.
Can you tell us; those nightmares and evil spirits that were tormenting you -
are you still experiencing that?
I know I am free now.
I have peace and I can sleep all night without taking tablets.
I don’t have nightmares anymore and I realise that everything I did was influenced by demons.
I thank God for setting me free from that spirit of control and manipulation that hurt my husband.
She said that ever since her deliverance, she has not had any of those nightmares.
She can sleep without taking tablets.
Before, she had to take tablets to be able to sleep.
Now she can sleep freely all night; there is no problem, no nightmare.
Those spirits are not tormenting her anymore.
Now she knows that that anger that was causing problems in her marriage has left her
and she knows she is free.
All those evil spirits that entered her right from birth are gone, in Jesus' name.
So, we give thanks to God for your wonderful deliverance.
We know the people want to learn from you.
What word of advice would you give people that think they can never be free?
How can you advise them?
Mrs Ionara
Deliverance Testimony
Many people think that if you have a satanic covenant that you can never be free.
Witchcraft is a bondage because if you don’t do what they ask you to, they attack you.
I want to tell you that there is a way out – Jesus sets us free and gives us peace of heart.
It is a completely different life – a totally new feeling to the one I had before.
She said she wants to advise people that it is possible to be free.
Before, she didn't think she could ever be free from that satanic covenant.
She thought that if you have that connection with those evil spirits,
whether it is different types of magic, witchcraft, spirit of death in a cemetery
or this connection with demons, she didn't ever think she could be free.
But now she knows that yes, you can receive freedom.
That Jesus can break that covenant from satan
and Jesus can give you peace and joy.
Now she feels totally different.
Thank You, Jesus.
We want to thank God for your life and give glory to God for this wonderful deliverance.
Hallelujah - let's clap for Jesus!
TT ROBERT BEGIER 05/10/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 20/10/2018